<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ideacode on Agile technology solutions that work for you, the spaces you manage, and the people who use them. | ideacode Software</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Ideacode on Agile technology solutions that work for you, the spaces you manage, and the people who use them. | ideacode Software</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:25:40 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lightweight Website Initiative</title><link>/lwi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:52:56 -0500</pubDate><guid>/lwi/</guid><description>Lightweight Website Initiative Count every bit or every bit counts
What is a lightweight website? A lightweight website strives to be efficient and slim. It uses the minimal necessary html, css, js, in order to render and deliver content.
Why does it matter? Every bit has multiple costs. There is the initial cost of the server to process the request and generate the response. The response is then transmitted through the internet to the client&amp;rsquo;s browser.</description></item><item><title>Roundcube</title><link>/roundcube/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 06:18:19 -0400</pubDate><guid>/roundcube/</guid><description>Access to email on the web has moved to a new location. Please visit our new email location at https://mail.ideacode.com, and make sure to update your bookmarks. If you stored your password in your browser, your browser may not know how to provide your password on the new location. If you need help with your password, please call your ideacode support representative.</description></item><item><title>ideacode will present at the 2012 CFTA conference</title><link>/news/1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 18:57:10 -0400</pubDate><guid>/news/1/</guid><description>&lt;p>ideacode will present at the &lt;a href="http://cfta.org">2012 CFTA conference&lt;/a>:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Lifting the Space Planning Blues&lt;/strong>:&lt;br>
How NC State University completed a massive space analysis by switching from hand-colored plans to automated coloring&lt;br>
(Tuesday August 7, 2012 &amp;ndash; 9:45-10:45 am / Computer-Aided Facilities Management)&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Building a Better GIS&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
Harnessing the opportunity of GIS on mobile devices and tablet computers, while serving the needs of big desktop.&lt;br>
(Tuesday August 7, 2012 &amp;ndash; 1:15-2:15 pm / GIS)&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Hope to see you there! Check us out at booth #12.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>